作词 : Ren Zotto
作曲 : Ren Zotto
Faded hues, I've been going through it
褪色的世界 早已被我习惯
There must be something about you
你一定有什么特别之处
About you
在你身上
It was new, curious but true, darling
听上去很新奇但这是真的，亲爱的
But quickly something I outgrew
但很快我就不再需要它了
Now I need a one-way ticket from your world, yeah
现在 我需要一张从你世界离开的单程票
Overstayed my welcome, I'm a burden
我知道是我逾期待得太久，成了负担
Wanna take a picture when I'm hurting?
想记录下我受伤的样子吗？
I'm a better villain when I'm burning
感到灼痛时我是更好的反派
Never gonna be the one to shake your world view
我永远不会成为颠覆你世界观的那个人
That one's on you, that one's on you
它只取决于你，只属于你
I only wanted to hold you briefly
我只是想短暂地拥你入怀
It's irreversible damage that I've done
是我造成无法挽回的伤害
While passing by I crash-landed in your reach
当我经过时坠落在你领地
I don't belong here, I don't belong in your
我不属于这里，不属于你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, oh oh, in your
大气层，大气层，哦 哦，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, here in your
空气里，空气里，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, oh oh, in your
大气层，大气层，哦 哦，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, here
空气里，空气里，这里
Tired of painting in shades of blue
早就厌烦了用蓝色调作画
I don't wanna fuck with you
我不想和你纠缠
Wanna slip by, wanna cut ties
想悄悄溜走，想切断联系
Dematerialize
就这样消散
Tell me who to trust, go and make a fuss, technicoloured husk
告诉我该信任谁，去制造麻烦，色彩斑斓的外壳
Gotta break my heart and never let me readjust
必须让我心碎让我永远无法恢复
I just gotta get away from your influence
我只需要摆脱你的影响力
Need a one-way ticket from your world, yeah
我需要一张从你世界离开的单程票
Overstayed my welcome, I'm a burden
我知道是我逾期待得太久，成了负担
Wanna take a picture when I'm hurting?
想记录下我受伤的样子吗？
I'm a better villain when I'm burning
感到灼痛时我是更好的反派
Never gonna be the one to shake your world view
我永远不会成为颠覆你世界观的那个人
That one's on you, that one's on you
它只取决于你，只属于你
I only wanted to hold you briefly
我只是想短暂地拥你入怀
It's irreversible damage that I've done
是我造成无法挽回的伤害
While passing by I crash-landed in your reach
当我经过时坠落在你领地
I don't belong here, I don't belong here
我不属于这里，不属于这里
I only wanted to hold you briefly
我只是想短暂地拥你入怀
It's irreversible damage that I've done
是我造成无法挽回的伤害
While passing by I crash-landed in your reach
当我经过时坠落在你领地
I don't belong here, I don't belong in your
我不属于这里，不属于你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, oh oh, in your
大气层，大气层，哦 哦，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, here in your
空气里，空气里，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, oh oh, in your
大气层，大气层，哦 哦，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, here
空气里，空气里，这里
Now you can think about me
现在你终于可以考虑我了
But you've been making me sick, a habit I gotta kick
但你总令我不适，这习惯需要改改
Our energy don't click no more
我们的能量不再无法契合
No more, no more
不再，不再
I don't belong here
我不属于这里
I don't belong in your
我不属于你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, oh oh, in your
大气层，大气层，哦 哦，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, here in your
空气里，空气里，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, oh oh, in your
大气层，大气层，哦 哦，在你的
Atmosphere, atmosphere, here
空气里，空气里，这里